[{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678922768,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":25000,"timeElapsed":165637},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678937171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":14401,"timeElapsed":180040},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678946277,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":9103,"timeElapsed":189146},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678952306,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6027,"timeElapsed":195175},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678965441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":13133,"timeElapsed":208310},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678972921,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":7477,"timeElapsed":215790},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678981609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":8686,"timeElapsed":224478},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678987335,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":5723,"timeElapsed":230204},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678991934,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":4597,"timeElapsed":234803},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679002425,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":7672,"timeElapsed":245293},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679007788,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":5361,"timeElapsed":250657},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679011448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3657,"timeElapsed":254317},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679014366,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2916,"timeElapsed":257235},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679018543,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":4174,"timeElapsed":261411},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679022437,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3890,"timeElapsed":265306},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679028472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":6032,"timeElapsed":271341},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679037977,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9503,"timeElapsed":280846},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679041353,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3373,"timeElapsed":284222},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679043972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2614,"timeElapsed":286841},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679054491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8753,"timeElapsed":297360},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679056900,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2406,"timeElapsed":299769},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679059748,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2846,"timeElapsed":302617},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679062146,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2396,"timeElapsed":305015},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679065249,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3100,"timeElapsed":308118},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679067809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2556,"timeElapsed":310678},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679070924,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3114,"timeElapsed":313793},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679073942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3012,"timeElapsed":316811},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679076472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2528,"timeElapsed":319341},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679081864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3583,"timeElapsed":324733},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679091320,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":9453,"timeElapsed":334189},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679094374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3052,"timeElapsed":337243},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679096931,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2554,"timeElapsed":339800},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679101087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4154,"timeElapsed":343955},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679105003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3914,"timeElapsed":347871},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679107882,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2877,"timeElapsed":350751},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679110873,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2989,"timeElapsed":353742},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679115170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4295,"timeElapsed":358039},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679134112,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":17433,"timeElapsed":376981},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679138134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4020,"timeElapsed":381003},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679144815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6679,"timeElapsed":387684},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679148952,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4135,"timeElapsed":391821},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679157530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":8575,"timeElapsed":400399},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679163745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":6213,"timeElapsed":406614},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679168385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4637,"timeElapsed":411254},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679171923,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3535,"timeElapsed":414792},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679175529,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3603,"timeElapsed":418397},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679187209,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9900,"timeElapsed":430078},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679190247,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3037,"timeElapsed":433116},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679192718,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2468,"timeElapsed":435587},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679195165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2445,"timeElapsed":438034},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679197430,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2264,"timeElapsed":440299},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679200442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3011,"timeElapsed":443311},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679203294,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2849,"timeElapsed":446162},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679206047,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2751,"timeElapsed":448916},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679210109,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4061,"timeElapsed":452978},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679214589,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3085,"timeElapsed":457458},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679219283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4691,"timeElapsed":462152},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679221926,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2640,"timeElapsed":464795},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679224398,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2470,"timeElapsed":467267},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679226886,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2486,"timeElapsed":469755},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679234211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":7322,"timeElapsed":477080},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679237683,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3469,"timeElapsed":480552},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679241088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3402,"timeElapsed":483957},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679244635,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3545,"timeElapsed":487504},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679253210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6949,"timeElapsed":496079},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679256389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3177,"timeElapsed":499258},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679261901,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5510,"timeElapsed":504770},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679264623,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2720,"timeElapsed":507492},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679267562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2937,"timeElapsed":510431},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679272626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5062,"timeElapsed":515495},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679277302,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4670,"timeElapsed":520171},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679280300,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2996,"timeElapsed":523169},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679283412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":3110,"timeElapsed":526281},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679286102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2688,"timeElapsed":528971},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679290287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2750,"timeElapsed":533156},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679292822,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2533,"timeElapsed":535691},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679304277,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":11454,"timeElapsed":547146},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679307631,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3351,"timeElapsed":550500},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679316889,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":9256,"timeElapsed":559758},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679319431,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2539,"timeElapsed":562300},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679322244,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2809,"timeElapsed":565113},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679325113,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2867,"timeElapsed":567982},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679327820,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2705,"timeElapsed":570689},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679333464,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":4202,"timeElapsed":576333},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679340442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":6977,"timeElapsed":583311},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679343172,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2727,"timeElapsed":586041},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679345455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2281,"timeElapsed":588324},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679348264,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2807,"timeElapsed":591133},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679351053,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2787,"timeElapsed":593922},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679356985,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":5929,"timeElapsed":599854},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679359506,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2519,"timeElapsed":602375},{"subjectID":"u9z03qtv5u","prolificID":"6760ec1e724b0f741fb8ba68","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2569e5abd57144508f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679362762,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":3254,"timeElapsed":605631}]